
module.exports = [

   {
      question: "Who holds the record for the highest score by a batsman in an inning in Test cricket?",
      options: ["Brian Lara", "Don Bradman", "Virendra Sehwag", "Kumar Sangakkara"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   }

   ,
   {
      question: "Which country won the first ICC Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
      options: ["West Indies", "Australia", "India", "England"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },
   {
      question: "Who is the fastest bowler to reach 400 wickets in ODI cricket?",
      options: ["Wasim Akram", "Brett Lee", "Shane Bond", "Muttiah Muralitharan"],
      correctAnswer: 1
   },
   {
      question: "Which player has scored the most runs in a single ODI match?",
      options: ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Virat Kohli", "Rohit Sharma", "AB de Villiers"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Which country has won the most ICC T20 World Cups?",
      options: ["India", "Australia", "West Indies", "England"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Who is the only player to have scored 100 international centuries?",
      options: ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Ricky Ponting", "Kumar Sangakkara", "Brian Lara"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Who was the first batsman to score a century in a Twenty20 international match?",
      options: ["Matthew Hayden", "Brendon McCullum", "Chris Gayle", "David Warner"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Who was the first batsman to score 1000 runs in an IPL?",
      options: ["Chris Gayle", "Virat Kohli", "David Warner", "Shaun Marsh"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Which bowler has the best bowling figures in a Test match?",
      options: ["Jim Laker", "Muttiah Muralitharan", "Anil Kumble", "Shane Warne"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   }
   ,
   {
      question: "Which cricketer has the most number of wickets in T20 internationals?",
      options: ["Shane Bond", "Brett Lee", "Lasith Malinga", "Dwayne Bravo"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   }

];